{
    "id": "dfa79913b8fe4c0faa68aa389b655ef9",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Walk carefully ………………. you should fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lest",
                "otherwise",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8789f930336f48a38a63ecdb98c0f0fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. he saw me, he started yelling.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner than",
                "As soon as",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45da6be6468649229a9e9f27d4c2f35a"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… did the police reach the spot than the crowd dispersed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "As soon as",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "36dbbcd1ddcb41abbe740fa86a48a192"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the same crook ………….. cheated me last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfa97361c6bf4f6fbe140f86bfb970c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is honest ………………… industrious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "also",
                "as well as",
                "as well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "53bc4dead35c40ecbf08b8f3c0ae1d80"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. harshly your parents may treat you, you must respect them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "As though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15d6368b98494e0fab2c1696bb1bed18"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wise men seek knowledge …………….. the ignorant shun it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "however",
                "whereas"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "84cc98e0d0fc40aabdc99f45f9b1daa9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me ……………….. I could lend her my camera.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "in case",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f3480b7b7ce44aca199ac9385a45b6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had hardly recovered from pneumonia, …………….. he suffered a heart attack.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "than",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f894830756c04b19866b896525efde9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "A Rajput soldier ……………….. die than surrender.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "would rather",
                "rather"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f99100b7928463baca6494f0bd4f0ba"
        }
    ]
}